[music]
[Instructor] You know, if you take
the word Unity and add an R sound,
you get Unitry, which kind
of sounds like unit three.
It's a pretty amazing coincidence,
because we are about to start Unit 3.
In this Unit, we will create
a beautiful, fast-paced,
endless side-scrolling game
where the player needs to jump
over obstacles in their path.
[music] [game sounds]
[explosion]
Now, as you were watching
and listening to that,
you probably noticed
that it felt a lot more polished
than either of our previous prototypes.
That's because it had Animation,
Sound,
and Particle Effects.
Did you see the character
running, jumping,
and dramatically falling over?
Did you hear the Sound Effects
and Music in the background?
Did you see the little Particle
Effects kicking up from the back
of the character's feet and the massive
explosion at the end? [explosion]
It's these little touches
that will take your good Project
and make it great. These elements
help immerse the player
in the environment you've created.
Being able to add them
to your Projects
will be a literal game changer.
So let's start creating.
[music]